Better set your watch, you don’t wanna miss…
Ben 10: Secret of the Omnitrix is a animation, science
fiction, family film directed by Scooter Tidwell.
After a battle with Dr.
Animo in a power plant, Ben notices something strange is
happening with the Omnitrix but doesn't tell anyone.
Tetrax arrives and tells them the Omnitrix is
broadcasting a self-destruct signal.
Tetrax and Ben go to find the creator of the Omnitrix to fix it
before it destroys itself and the universe along with it.
Gwen stows away to help her cousin.
Ben Tennyson (voice), played by Tara Strong.
Gwen Tennyson (voice), played by Meagan Moore.
Grandpa Max (voice), played by Paul Eiding.
Four Arms (voice), played by Richard McGonagle.
Azmuth (voice), played by Robert David Hall.
Cannonbolt / Way Big (voice), played by Fred Tatasciore.
The Ben 10 films are a series of American animated and live-action, fictional superhero films produced by Cartoon Network Studios set in
the fictional franchise, Ben 10 conceived by Man of Action, produced by Cartoon Network Studios, and owned by Warner Bros.
Entertainment.
As of 2020, there has been three animated films – Secret of the Omnitrix (2007), Destroy All Aliens (2012), Versus the
Universe (2020) and two live-action films  – Race Against Time (2007), Alien Swarm (2009) released in the franchise.
The film explores themes of extraterrestrial technology,
superhero, transformation, alien, based on cartoon.
The tone is thought_provoking.